<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.cevelop.elevator.feature"
      label="Elevator"
      version="1.14.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="IFS Institute for Software"
      license-feature="com.cevelop.license.feature"
      license-feature-version="1.14.0.qualifier">

   <description url="https://www.cevelop.com/features">
      Elevator is a Plug-in for Eclipse CDT that helps refactor existing
C++ code towards the C++11 ISO standard. It currently provides
programmer assistance for migrating variable declarations and
initializations to the new uniform initialization syntax.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2014 IFS Institute for Software
Copyright (c) 2021 The Authors of Cevelop
This program and the accompanying materials are made available
under the terms of the Eclipse Public License 2.0 which accompanies
this distribution, and is available at https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-2.0/
SPDX-License-Identifier: EPL-2.0
   </copyright>

   <license url="https://www.cevelop.com/license">
      Cevelop License Agreement

This is a legal agreement between you, the end user, and Hochschule für Technik
Rapperswil HSR, hereinafter referred to as &quot;HSR&quot;. Elevator (the &quot;Software&quot;) is
owned by HSR and is protected by copyright law. Upon acceptance of the terms of
this License Agreement, your rights and obligations with respect to use of the
Software are as follows.

COPYRIGHT.

The Software and Documentation are copyrighted by HSR and are protected by
international copyright laws. The product contains copyrighted software of HSR.
All rights reserved. You agree not to remove any trademarks or copyright notices
from the Software or Documentation.

OTHER RESTRICTIONS.

You may not disclose, publish, translate, rent, lease, transfer, export or
otherwise make the Software available in any form, to any person or entity,
except as expressly licensed herein. You may not reverse engineer, decompile
or disassemble the Software.

You cannot use HSR or related names, logos or trademarks to market your
software without express written permission.

IN NO EVENT SHALL HSR BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OF PROFIT OR ANY OTHER
DAMAGE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR
OTHER DAMAGES. THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND.
HSR SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED,
INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE.

HSR DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS
OR THAT THE OPERATION OF THE SOFTWARE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE.

GOVERNING LAW.

This Agreement shall be governed by Swiss law, without regard to conflict of
laws principles. This Agreement may only be modified by a written document
signed by the party or parties to be bound. Except as may be specified in such a
written agreement, this is the entire agreement between you and HSR and all
other terms are rejected. You agree not to use, ship, or export the Software in
violation of any applicable law.

In the event of any legal disputes in conjunction with this license and
contracts based on it, the courts of Rapperswil/SG shall be the sole competent
courts.

ENTIRE AGREEMENT.

You agree that this Agreement expresses the entire understanding between you and
HSR, and supersedes all other communications, oral or written, relating to the
Software.

COPYRIGHT 2017 Hochschule für Technik Rapperswil

MANUFACTURER:
HSR Hochschule für Technik Rapperswil
Oberseestrasse 10
Postfach 1475
8640 Rapperswil
Switzerland
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Cevelop Internal Update Site" url="https://www.cevelop.com/internal/latest"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.codan.core" version="2.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.codan.core.cxx" version="1.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.codan.ui" version="2.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.codan.ui.cxx" version="2.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.core" version="5.3.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources" version="3.7.100" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.codan.checkers" version="3.2.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.codan.checkers.ui" version="1.1.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ltk.core.refactoring" version="3.5.200" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text" version="3.7.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide" version="3.7.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.workbench"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface" version="3.9.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ltk.ui.refactoring" version="3.7.100" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.cdt.ui" version="5.7.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="com.cevelop.elevator"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
